Guide to the News Service subject files, 1930-ongoing
Duke University. University Archives
- Container List
  - Biochemistry, 1991- (Box 112)
  - Biotechnology, 1994- (Box 112)
  - Cancer, 1999, 2000 (Box 112)
  - Students-Individual Subjects (Box 112)
  - Study Abroad Program, 1991- (Box 112)
  - Summer Programs, 1992- (Box 112)
  - Summer Session, 1991- (Box 112)
  - Symposia, General, 1991- (Box 112)
  - Tel-Com, 1989- (Box 112)
  - Tenure, 1992- (Box 112)
  - Terry Sanford Institute of Public Policy, 2001- (Box 112)
  - TIP (Talent Identification Program), 1994- (Box 112)
  - Triangle Universities Licensing Consortium, 1989- (Box 112)
  - Triangle University Center for Advanced Studies (TUCAS), 1989 - (Box 112)
  - Triangle University Computation Center (TUCC), 1989- (Box 112)
  - Triangle University Nuclear Lab (TUNL), 1992 (Box 112)
  - Tropical Studies, Organizations for, 1991- (Box 112)
  - Trustees, General, 2001- (Box 112)
  - Tuition, 2000- (Box 112)
  - Union, 1992-1995, 1996- (Box 112)
  - United Way Fund, 1989- (Box 112)
  - University Seal, 1993- (Box 112)
  - VA Hospital (Box 112)
  - Visiting Journalists, 1991- (Box 112)
  - Volunteers, 2000- (Box 112)
  - Washington Duke Inn, 1991, 1994- (Box 112)
  - Wetlands Center, 1994- (Box 112)
  - Wind Symphony, 1992- (Box 112)
  - Women's Center, 1996- (Box 112)
  - Women's Studies Program, 1994-1995, 1996- (Box 112)
  - Zoology, 1991- (Box 112)
  - Cardiology, 2000 (Box 113)
  - Cell Biology, 2000- (Box 113)
  - Center for the Severely Hearing Impaired, 1991 (Box 113)
  - Children's Cancer Center, 1991 (Box 113)
  - Children's Hospital, 2000- (Box 113)
  - Community and Family Medicine, 1991 (Box 113)
  - Cystic Fibrosis Center, 1991 (Box 113)
  - Dermatology, 1991 (Box 113)
  - Diabetes, 1991 (Box 113)
  - Diet and Fitness Center, 1994-, 1996- (Box 113)
  - Division of Reproductive Endocrinology and Infertility, 1991 (Box 113)
  - DUPAC, 1992 (Box 113)
  - Ear, Nose and Throat, 1991 (Box 113)
  - Emergency, 2000- (Box 113)
  - Endoscopy, 1991 (Box 113)
  - Environmental Medicine, 1991 (Box 113)
  - Eye Center, 1994- (Box 113)
  - Family Practice Program, 1991 (Box 113)
  - Genetics, 1999- (Box 113)
  - Gerontology (Study of Aging), 1992 (Box 113)
  - Health Administration, 1991- (Box 113)
  - Health Night Out Series, 1991 (Box 113)
  - Helicopter Program, 1992 (Box 113)
  - Hematology-Oncology, 1991 (Box 113)
  - Hospital: Sea Level, 1992 (Box 113)
  - Hyperbaric Oxygenation Chamber, 1991 (Box 113)
  - Implants, 1991 (Box 113)
  - Infectious Diseases, Center for, 1991 (Box 113)
  - Kidney, 1992- (Box 113)
  - Malpractice Suits/Claims, 2000- (Box 113)
  - Medical Center Library, 1991 (Box 113)
  - Medical Psychology, 1991 (Box 113)
  - Microbiology and Immunology, 1992 (Box 113)
  - Neurobiology, 1995-, 1996- (Box 113)
  - Neurology, 1998 (Box 113)
  - Nuclear Medicine and Training, 1991 (Box 113)
  - Nursing Services, 1991-, 1997- (Box 113)
  - Nutritional Studies, Center for, 1991 (Box 113)
  - Obstetrics and Gynecology, 1994- (Box 113)
  - Occupational Health Service, 1991 (Box 113)
  - Office of Med. Ctr. Science and Technology (Box 113)
  - Admissions, 1997- (Box 114)
  - African-American Studies, 1995-1996 (Box 114)
  - Alumni/Alumni Affairs, 1999 (Box 114)
  - American Dance Festival, 1999-2000 (Box 114)
  - Art Museum, 1999-2000 (Box 114)
  - Art/Art History, 1997-2000 (Box 114)
  - Artist Series, 1992 (Box 114)
  - Awards, 1994-1996 (Box 114)
  - Budget and Finance, 1994-1996 (Box 114)
  - Buildings and Grounds, 1995-1996 (Box 114)
  - Center for Documentary Studies, 1999 (Box 114)
  - Ophthalmology, 1991, 1994 - (Box 114)
  - Organ Donor, 1991 (Box 114)
  - Orthopedics, 1991 (Box 114)
  - Osteoporosis, 1991 (Box 114)
  - Pathology, 1991 (Box 114)
  - Pediatrics, 2000 (Box 114)
  - Pharmacology, 2000- (Box 114)
  - Physical Therapy, 1992 (Box 114)
  - Physician's Associate and Assistant Programs, 1991- (Box 114)
  - Poison Control Center, 1991 (Box 114)
  - Primary Health Care Unit, 1991 (Box 114)
  - Prosthetics and Orthotics, 1991- (Box 114)
  - Psychiatry, 2000 (Box 114)
  - Radiology, 1994- (Box 114)
  - Respiratory Therapy, 1991 (Box 114)
  - Ronald McDonald House, 1988-1990, 1994- (Box 114)
  - Sickle Cell Anemia Study, 1992 (Box 114)
  - Sleep Disorders, 1991 (Box 114)
  - Special Cases, 1997 (Box 114)
  - Speech and Hearing, 1991 (Box 114)
  - Surgery, 1999-2000 (Box 114)
  - Teer House, 1992 (Box 114)
  - Transplants, 1996, 1997-1998 (Box 114)
  - Urology, 1991 (Box 114)
  - Center for Study of Communications and Journalism, 1992-1999 (Box 115)
  - Chapel, Duke, 1998-1999 (Box 115)
  - Chemistry, 1994-1999 (Box 115)
  - Ciompi Quartet, 1994-1996 (Box 115)
  - Children's Classic, 1993-1999 (Box 115)
  - Computer Science, 1993-1999 (Box 115)
  - Continuing Education, 1997-1999 (Box 115)
  - Curriculum, 1997-1998 (Box 115)
  - Divinity School, 1998 (Box 115)
  - Broadway at Duke, 1997 (Box 115)
  - Drama Program, 1997 (Box 115)
  - Drugs and Alcohol, 1999-2999 (Box 115)
  - Duke Endowment, 1997 (Box 115)
  - Duke Endowment, 1996 (Box 115)
  - Duke Forest, 1997-1998 (Box 115)
  - Duke, James Buchanan, 1993 (Box 115)
  - Duke, Doris, 1994- (Box 115)
  - Duke University, General, 1999-2000 (Box 115)
  - Duke Univ. Historical Data, 1999-2000 (Box 115)
  - Duke Univ. Press, 1993-1996 (Box 115)
  - Economics, 1994-1996 (Box 115)
  - Editorials/Letters, 2000 (Box 115)
  - Employees, General, 1998 (Box 115)
  - Endowment, 1996 (Box 115)
  - Employee Benefits, 1997-1998 (Box 115)
  - Engineering, 1997-1999 (Box 115)
  - Facilities and Planning, 1995-1998 (Box 115)
  - Faculty Appointments and Promotions, 1994-1999 (Box 115)
  - Faculty and Staff, General, 1997-98 (Box 115)
  - Film and Video Program, 1993 (Box 115)
  - Film And Video Program, 1992 (Box 115)
  - Films/Filmed on Campus, 1997-1998 (Box 115)
  - Financial Aid, 1994- (Box 115)
  - Former Employees, 1993-1996 (Box 115)
  - Founders' Day/Society, 1996 (Box 115)
  - Fraternities and Sororities, 1996 (Box 115)
  - Freshmen/Freshmen Activities, 1996 (Box 115)
  - Fuqua School, 2000 (Box 115)
  - Fuqua School of Business, 1999 (Box 115)
  - Fundraising, 1998 (Box 116)
  - Gardens, 2000 (Box 116)
  - Gardens, 1999 (Box 116)
  - Gender Relations, 1995- (Box 116)
  - Gifts, 2000 (Box 116)
  - Gifts, 1999 (Box 116)
  - Grants, 1999- (Box 116)
  - History, 1997 (Box 116)
  - Honorary Degree Recipients, 1997- (Box 116)
  - Housing, 1995- (Box 116)
  - Human Resources, 1993- (Box 116)
  - Institute of the Arts, 1995 (Box 116)
  - International Affairs, 1994-1997 (Box 116)
  - Jazz, 1992-1993 (Box 116)
  - Latin American Studies, 1992- (Box 116)
  - Law School, 2000 (Box 116)
  - Law School, 1999 (Box 116)
  - Law School, 1998 (Box 116)
  - Lectures/Speakers, 1997-2000 (Box 116)
  - Major Speakers, 1997-2000 (Box 116)
  - Marine Lab, 1991-1996 (Box 116)
  - Medical Center, General, 2000 (Box 116)
  - Medical Center, General, 1999- (Box 116)
  - Dept. of Medicine, 1996 (Box 116)
  - Faculty Minorities (Box 116)
  - Minoritiy Affairs--Racial Issues, Relations, 1998-2000 (Box 116)
  - Music, 1997 (Box 116)
  - Perkins Library System, 1998-2000 (Box 116)
  - Physics, 1994-2000 (Box 116)
  - Policies and Regulations, 1992 (Box 116)
  - Political Science, 1997- (Box 116)
  - Primate Center, 1997 (Box 116)
  - Program in Ethics, 1995-1996 (Box 116)
  - Psychology, 1994 (Box 116)
  - Psychology, 1993 (Box 116)
  - Public Safety/Crime, 1999-2000 (Box 117)
  - Rankings, 1997-1999 (Box 117)
  - Religion, 1995-1996 (Box 117)
  - Religious Activities, 1992-1995 (Box 117)
  - Romance Languages and Literature, 1991-1994 (Box 117)
  - Scholarships, General, 1997-2000 (Box 117)
  - School of the Environment, 1998-2000 (Box 117)
  - Students, General, 1998-2000 (Box 117)
  - Duke Student Government, 1996-1997 (Box 117)
  - Students, Accomplishments, 2000 (Box 117)
  - Students, Committees, 1991-1995 (Box 117)
  - Students, Deaths, 1994-1995 (Box 117)
  - Students, Health, 1993 (Box 117)
  - Students, Honors and Awards, 1996 (Box 117)
  - Students, Political, 2000 (Box 117)
  - Students, Political, 1999 (Box 117)
  - Students, Prospective, 1996-2000 (Box 117)
  - Students, Organizaions, 1992 (Box 117)
  - TIP, 1993 (Box 117)
  - TIP, 1992 (Box 117)
  - Terry Sanford Institute, 1998-2000 (Box 117)
  - Trustees, General, 1998-2000 (Box 117)
  - Tuition, 1997-1999 (Box 117)
  - Volunteers, 1996-1999 (Box 117)
  - Women's Center, 1993 (Box 117)
  - Women's Studies Program, 1993 (Box 117)
  - Women's Studies Program and Women's Center, 1992 (Box 117)
  - Alumni, 1992, 1995-1995, 1997, 2001 (Box 118)
  - Athletics, 1995 (Box 118)
  - Bryan University Center, 1981, undated (Box 118)
  - China Encounter Photos, 1976 (Box 118)
  - Cape Hatteras- Research Vessel, 1980-1982, 1984-1986 (Box 118)
  - Cape Hatteras- Research Vessel, 1981, undated (Box 118)
  - Center on Law, Ethics and National Security, 1994-1995, 2001 (Box 118)
  - Center for LBGT Life, 1998 (Box 118)
  - Center for the Study of Medical Ethics and Humanities, 2002 (Box 118)
  - Children's Classic, 1985-1987 (Box 118)
  - Chinese Visit, 1984, undated (Box 118)
  - Chinese Encounter Photos, 1976 (Box 118)
  - Chronicle 75th Anniversary, 1980 (2 folders) (Box 118)
  - Chronicle 75th Anniversary- Agenda and Participants, 1980 (Box 118)
  - Chronicle 75th Anniversary- James D. Barber Questionaire, undated (Box 118)
  - Chronicle 75th Anniversary- Initial Responses, 1980 (Box 118)
  - Chronicle 75th Anniversary- Responses to 75th Chronicle Reunion, 1980-1981 (Box 118)
  - Chronicle 75th Anniversary- Invitations, 1980 (Box 118)
  - Chronicle 75th Anniversary- Budget and Correspondence, 1980 (Box 118)
  - Chronicle 80th Anniversary- No's, 1985 (Box 118)
  - Chronicle 80th Anniversary- Yes's, 1985 (Box 118)
  - Chronicle 80th Anniversary- Budget, 1985-1986 (Box 118)
  - Chronicle 80th Anniversary- Letters, 1985 (Box 118)
  - Chronicle 80th Anniversary, 1980, 1984-1985 (Box 118)
  - Chronicle 80th Anniversary, 1985, undated (Box 118)
  - Chronicle 80th Anniversary, 1985, undated (Box 118)
  - Chronicle 80th Anniversary, 1980, 1985, undated (Box 118)
  - Conferences, 1998 (Box 118)
  - Divinity School, 1993-1995 (Box 118)
  - Drama Program, 1992-1993, 1995 (Box 118)
  - Duke News Service, 1982-1985, undated (Box 118)
  - Duke News Service, 1978-1981, 1983, undated (Box 118)
  - Duke Press, 1995 (Box 118)
  - Founder's Day, 14 December 1994 (Box 118)
  - History, 1995 (Box 118)
  - Inauguration, 1985 (Box 118)
  - Medical Center, General, 1959, 1995 (Box 118)
  - Medical Center, Psychiatry, 1995 (Box 118)
  - Minority Affairs, 2001 (Box 118)
  - NC Press Association, 1983-1986 (Box 119)
  - NC Press Association, 1981-1983, 1985 (Box 119)
  - NC Press Association, 1981, 1983-1986 (Box 119)
  - NC Press Association-Speech, 1982 (Box 119)
  - Perkins Library, 1993 (Box 119)
  - Photonics Center, 2001 (Box 119)
  - Women's Studies, 1992 (Box 119)
  - Students- Political Activities, 1977 (Box 119)
  - Students- Political Activities, 1978 (Box 119)
  - Students- Political Activities, 1979 (Box 119)
  - Students- Political Activities, 1980 (Box 119)
  - Students- Political Activities, 1981 (Box 119)
  - Students- Political Activities, 1982 (Box 119)
  - Students- Political Activities, 1984 (Box 119)
  - Students- Political Activities, 1985 (Box 119)
  - Students- Political Activities, 1986 (Box 119)
  - Miscellaneous Photographs, undated (Box 119)
  - Miscellaneous Photographs, undated (Box 119)
  - British American Festival, 1984- news clippings (2 folders) (Box 119)
  - Carol and Eric Meyers- photo, slides, and negatives, 1995, undated (Box 119)
  - Blackburn Literary Festival, 1978, 1981, 1983, 1985-1986, 1998 (Box 119)
  - Department of Medicine, 1988 (Box 120)
  - Retired/Deceased employees, 1995-1996 (Box 120)
  - AIDS Research, 1995 (Box 120)
  - Alzheimer's Disease, 1995 (Box 120)
  - Animal Research, 1991 (Box 120)
  - Cancer, 1996 (Box 120)
  - Cardiology, 1995 (Box 120)
  - Cancer/Cancer Center, 1995 (Box 120)
  - Cardiology, 1996 (Box 120)
  - Neurology, 1996 (Box 120)
  - Neurology, 1994 (Box 120)
  - Pediatrics, 1996 (Box 120)
  - Pediatrics, 1995 (Box 120)
  - Pharmacology, 1992-1993 (Box 120)
  - Psychiatry, 1996 (Box 120)
  - Psychiatry, 1994-1995 (Box 120)
  - Surgery, 1995 (Box 120)
  - Surgery, 1992 (Box 120)
  - Radiology, 1992 (Box 120)
  - Eye Center (Box 120)
  - Transplants, 1994 (Box 120)
  - Transplants, 1995 (Box 120)
  - Nixon- Photographs from Law School (Box 121)
  - Nixon Library Controversy (Box 121)
  - Nixon Library- Editorials, Letters to the Editor, Political Cartoons (4 folders) (Box 121)
  - Nixon Library- Miscellaneous articles (2 folders) (Box 121)
  - 1990 Full Page News Stories (Box 122)
  - 1989 May-July Full Page News Stories (Box 122)
  - 1989 Aug.-Dec. Full Page News Stories (Box 122)
  - 1989 Jan.-April Full Page News Stories (Box 122)
  - 1988 Apr. Full Page News Stories (Box 122)
  - 1988 May Full Page News Stories (Box 122)
  - 1988 Feb. Full Page News Stories (Box 122)
  - 1988 Aug.-Oct. Full Page News Stories (Box 122)
  - 1988 Nov.- Dec. Full Page News Stories (Box 122)
  - 1988 Jan.-Feb. Full Page News Stories (Box 122)
  - 1987 Oct.-Dec. Full Page News Stories (Box 122)
  - 1987 Aug. Full Page News Stories (Box 122)
  - 1987 June-July Full Page News Stories (Box 122)
  - 1987 May Full Page News Stories (Box 122)
  - 1987 Mar.-Apr. Full Page News Stories (Box 122)
  - 1987 Jan.-Feb. Full Page News Stories (Box 122)
  - 1986 Dec.-1987 Jan. Full Page News Stories (Box 122)
  - 1986 Oct.-Nov. Full Page News Stories (Box 122)
  - 1986 Jul.-Sep. Full Page News Stories (Box 122)
  - 1986 Apr.-July Full Page News Stories (Box 122)
  - 1985 Apr.-1986 Apr. Full Page News Stories (Box 122)
  - 1985 Jan.-Apr. Full Page News Stories (Box 122)
  - 1984 Jul.-Dec. Full Page News Stories (Box 122)
  - 1984 Feb.-Jun. Full Page News Stories (Box 122)
  - Buildings and Construction, 1964-1965 (Box 123)
  - Campaign, 1965/1966 (Box 123)
  - Correspondence (Box 123)
  - Emergency Procedures (Box 123)
  - Faculty, General Info (Box 123)
  - Future Feature File (Box 123)
  - Medicine (Box 123)
  - Monthly Report of Inches (Box 123)
  - Praise (Box 123)
  - Physical Plant (Box 123)
  - Provost Meetings (Box 123)
  - Retirement Info. (Box 123)
  - Scholarship Info. (Box 123)
  - Woman's College (Box 123)
  - Address by Terry Sanford (Box 123)
  - Academic Council (Box 123)
  - Air Force Drug Studies, 1975 (Box 123)
  - Afro-American Studies (Box 123)
  - Asian-Pacific Center (Box 123)
  - Allen Building Takeover: 1969 Feb. (Box 123)
  - Athletics (Box 123)
  - Attrition Students (Box 123)
  - AAAS (Box 123)
  - Admissions (Box 123)
  - Brodie Statements (Box 123)
  - Buildings (Box 123)
  - Buildings (Box 123)
  - Business-Research Ties-Duke Policy (Box 123)
  - Black Students (Box 123)
  - Biological Sciences (Box 123)
  - Benefits (Box 123)
  - Budget Figures (Box 123)
  - Commencement, 1972 (Box 123)
  - Chamber of Commerce (Box 123)
  - Christie Report (Box 123)
  - College News Assn. (Box 123)
  - Crest St. (Box 123)
  - Chronicle (Box 123)
  - Chemistry (Box 123)
  - Cambodian Protect, 1970 Spring (Box 123)
  - Computer Sciences Dept. (Box 123)
  - Cost Accounting (Box 123)
  - Commencement Address, 1972 (Box 123)
  - Commencement, 1976 (Box 123)
  - Commencement, 1973 (Box 123)
  - Commencement, 1979 (Box 123)
  - Commencement, 1978 (Box 123)
  - Commencement, 1980 (Box 123)
  - Deferred Tuition (Box 123)
  - Duke Endowment (Box 123)
  - Enrollment Figures (Box 123)
  - Equipment, Office (Box 123)
  - Last Eastward Cruise (Box 123)
  - Energy Conservation (Box 123)
  - Equal Opportunity Report (Box 123)
  - Luis Ferrer (Box 123)
  - Football Program (Box 123)
  - Frats and Sororities (Box 123)
  - Futures, etc. (Box 123)
  - Graduation, 1982 (Box 123)
  - Graduation, 1987 (Box 123)
  - Graduation, 1986 May 4 (Box 123)
  - Graduation, 1985 (Box 123)
  - Graduation, 1984 (Box 123)
  - Graduation, 1981 (Box 123)
  - Graduation, 1976 (Box 123)
  - Graduate School Ratings (Box 124)
  - Graduate Training (Box 124)
  - Graduate Education and Graduate School (Box 124)
  - Carol Halstead (Box 124)
  - Hotel-Duke (Box 124)
  - Ken Hunter (Box 124)
  - Honor System (Box 124)
  - Ruth Harman Pix (Box 124)
  - Duke Hospital North (Box 124)
  - Hospital Union (Box 124)
  - Hyperbaric (Box 124)
  - Interns (Box 124)
  - Kodak Scholars (Box 124)
  - Labor Unions- Labor Problems (Box 124)
  - Media Tour-Triangle, 1987 (Box 124)
  - Marine Lab-Releases (Box 124)
  - Meetings, etc. (Box 124)
  - Monitor (Box 124)
  - Med Center Expansion (Box 124)
  - Miscellaneous (Box 124)
  - NASW- Joann Rogers (Box 124)
  - News Briefings (Box 124)
  - Nuclear Lab (Box 124)
  - Olympic Festival (Box 124)
  - Office (Box 124)
  - Organ Transplants (Box 124)
  - Op-ed project (Box 124)
  - Oceanography, General (Box 124)
  - Press Assn.- Press Banquet (Box 124)
  - Police Incidents (Box 124)
  - President's House (Box 124)
  - Pye's Hit List (Box 124)
  - Primate Facility (Box 124)
  - Public Safety, Parking (Box 124)
  - Phytotron (Box 124)
  - Pub Board Bylaws (Box 124)
  - Planning Comm.- University (Box 124)
  - Personnel Procedures (Box 124)
  - Policies, Procedures etc. (Box 124)
  - Retention Studies (Box 124)
  - Shroud of Turin (Box 124)
  - Stanford Release Program (Box 124)
  - Sanford Material (Box 124)
  - Science at Duke (Box 124)
  - Students- problems, etc. (Box 124)
  - Statements, etc. (Box 124)
  - South Africa Policies (Box 124)
  - Student Release Programs (Box 124)
  - Search Committees (Box 124)
  - Student Housing Etc, Student Programming (Box 124)
  - Staff Meeting Minutes (Box 124)
  - Sanford Pix (Box 124)
  - Teleram and Other Computers (Box 124)
  - Third Side of Triangle (Box 124)
  - Tuition, Fees, Ect. (Box 124)
  - University Wrapup Stories (Box 124)
  - University, General (Box 124)
  - Wall St. Journal, Admissions (Box 124)
  - Washington Post Fellows (Box 124)
  - Work Study Program (Box 124)
  - Nursing- Background Materials (Box 125)
  - Hospitals Administration Newsletter (Box 125)
  - Medical Alumni Newsletter (Box 125)
  - Hospital Costs Contest (Box 125)
  - Medical Library, Trent Connectionm, Etc. (Box 125)
  - Pharmacy Trainees Personal Information Sheets (Box 125)
  - Physical Training Personal Information Sheets (Box 125)
  - Dietic Interns Personal Information Sheets (Box 125)
  - X-Ray Technology Personal Information Sheets (Box 125)
  - Hospital Administration Interns Personal Information Sheets (Box 125)
  - Fallout- Disaster Training (Box 125)
  - Grants That Have Been Done (Box 125)
  - Nursing (2 folders) (Box 125)
  - Medical Center Miscellanous Groups and Individuals (Box 125)
  - Medical Center- Clinical (Box 125)
  - Medical Center- Research (Box 125)
  - Medical Center Facilities- Interior (Box 125)
  - Medical Center- Teaching (Box 125)
  - Medical Center Facilities- Exterior (Box 125)
  - Directory of North Carolina Newspapers, 1962 (Box 125)
  - Medical Background Data on Diseases (2 folders) (Box 125)
  - Medical Legislation (Box 125)
  - Medical Center- Miscellaneous (Box 125)
  - American Medical Association Medical Education-Background (Box 125)
  - Health Careers Congress, 1963 (2 folders) (Box 126)
  - Duke Medical Center Brochurs and Pamphlets (Box 126)
  - Magazines and Journals (Box 126)
  - Correspondence (Box 126)
  - Data on Hospital Incidents (Box 126)
  - Minutes- Department Heads and Administrative Staff Meetings (Box 126)
  - The Intercom (Box 126)
  - New Faculty Appointments-Lists That Have Been Done (Box 126)
  - Miscellaneous Materials (Box 126)
  - Medical Center- Miscellaneous Background Materials (Box 126)
  - Hospital and Medical School General Reference Materials (Box 126)
  - Hospital Constructions Newsletters (Box 126)
  - Duke University- Background Materials (Box 126)